For anyone who's been through surgery, you know it usually begins with a doctor telling you to count backwards from 10.
The first thought upon hearing this is that you're not tired at all, and this seems like not nearly enough time.
But then, funny enough, you make it to just seven, before the next thing you know, you're making up groggy in an entirely different room, hours later with the surgery completed.
Or at least that's most people's experience.
For an incredibly unlucky few, what comes next is one of the most disturbing things that can happen to a person.
Instead of waking up after the surgery, they wake up during the surgery.
What follows can only be described as a living nightmare.
Filled with a cocktail of medications to keep them from moving, they're awake, fully aware, and feeling everything.
But horrifyingly, they're also paralyzed and unable to move or tell anyone they're awake.
And they can feel every surgical instrument moving around inside them, and yet there's absolutely nothing they can do.
These are some of the horrifying incidents of people waking up during surgery.
And I'm gonna be honest with all of you.
This is a topic I knew about, but upon really getting into it, I found it to be so disturbing that I almost actually wish I didn't know about it after all.
So suffice to say, now more than ever, although the events in this video are fleeting and non-descriptive, they are still highly disturbing, so viewer discretion is strongly advised.
In 2008, 44 year old Donna of Manitoba went in for what was supposed to be a routine exploratory surgery.
She'd been battling severe abdominal pain and heavy bleeding for a while and doctors hoped to finally pinpoint.
The cause.
Donna had been under general anesthesia before and never had a problem, so she trusts the process.
After all the necessary preparations, a nurse wheeled her into the operating room, reassuring her with all the usual words, Don't worry, we'll take care of you.